<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vape Bible Juice Calc</string>
    <string name="main_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="create_new_recipe">Create New Recipe</string>
    <string name="how_to_help">How To/Help</string>
    <string name="log_in_register">Log in/ Register</string>
    <string name="my_saved_recipes">My Saved Recipes</string>
    <string name="example_recipes">Example Recipes</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_this_app">If you are new to DIY vaping, then this app may seem a little bit intimidating to you. I assure you that the Vape Bible Juice Calculator will make the process of creating your own recipes, and making you own E-Liquid as seemless as possible. Using this app only requires a few easy steps. First, you must decide what size bottle you will be making (conventional sizes are: 30mL, 60mL, and 120mL) Then, figure out what nicotine level and ratio you want your juice to be. When it comes to ratio\'s the higher VG content will make a smoother vape and more production, but will decrease the speed that it wicks into your atomizer. Next write down the Strength and ratio of the Nicotine base you wil be using. After that, come up with a flavor recipe using percent of total as the unit of measurement. You can find recipes online if you are struggling. Now just put all of that information into our calculator, and let us do all the rest of the work. The results page will tell you the exact measurements to put each ingredient into your mix.</string>
    <string name="flavor_mixing_tips">When it comes to mixing your own flavors, there are a few things you should remember. First of all, try not to overdo it on the amount of flavoring you put into the recipe. Typical recipes range from 10-20% for the total of all flavoring put into the recipe. Going any higher or lower than that will typically make your juice overwhelming or underwhelming. For each individual flavor concentrate, you need to consider how strong that particular concentrate is. A stronger concentrate, like many menthols or strong additives, will typically start to take over the entire flavor profile of the juice if more than 1 or 2% is added. On the other hand, more subtle flavors like TFA Strawberry(ripe) can typically be added as much as 10% before it starts to take over the flavor profile. The last tip on mixing flavors, is that your flavor will come out better if you mix several different types of the same flavor to create your own taste. Rather than putting one Strawberry flavor in your recipe and calling it good, try a mixture of several Strawberry concentrates, and maybe an additive to round out the flavor. This practice usually brings better flavor in the finished product.</string>
    <string name="viewPager_disclaimer">*Swipe right to see next page*</string>
</resources>
