<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vape Bible Juice Calc</string>
    <string name="main_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="create_new_recipe">Create New Recipe</string>
    <string name="how_to_help">How To/Help</string>
    <string name="log_in_register">Log in/ Register</string>
    <string name="my_saved_recipes">My Saved Recipes</string>
    <string name="example_recipes">Example Recipes</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_this_app">If you are new to DIY vaping, then this app may seem a little bit intimidating to you. I assure you that the Vape Bible Juice Calculator will make the process of creating your own recipes, and making you own E-Liquid as seemless as possible. Using this app only requires a few easy steps. First, you must decide what size bottle you will be making (conventional sizes are: 30mL, 60mL, and 120mL) Then, figure out what nicotine level and ratio you want your juice to be. When it comes to ratio\'s the higher VG content will make a smoother vape and more production, but will decrease the speed that it wicks into your atomizer. Next write down the Strength and ratio of the Nicotine base you wil be using. After that, come up with a flavor recipe using percent of total as the unit of measurement. You can find recipes online if you are struggling. Now just put all of that information into our calculator, and let us do all the rest of the work. The results page will tell you the exact measurements to put each ingredient into your mix.</string>
    <string name="flavor_mixing_tips">When it comes to mixing your own flavors, there are a few things you should remember. First of all, try not to overdo it on the amount of flavoring you put into the recipe. Typical recipes range from 10-20% for the total of all flavoring put into the recipe. Going any higher or lower than that will typically make your juice overwhelming or underwhelming. For each individual flavor concentrate, you need to consider how strong that particular concentrate is. A stronger concentrate, like many menthols or strong additives, will typically start to take over the entire flavor profile of the juice if more than 1 or 2% is added. On the other hand, more subtle flavors like TFA Strawberry(ripe) can typically be added as much as 10% before it starts to take over the flavor profile. The last tip on mixing flavors, is that your flavor will come out better if you mix several different types of the same flavor to create your own taste. Rather than putting one Strawberry flavor in your recipe and calling it good, try a mixture of several Strawberry concentrates, and maybe an additive to round out the flavor. This practice usually brings better flavor in the finished product.</string>
    <string name="viewPager_disclaimer">*Swipe right to see next page*</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="distributor_map">Distributor Map</string>
    <string name="common_shorthands">Sometimes, when looking at recipes written by other people, the recipe will use common shorthand for things like brands, and common flavors. Some may be easy enough to figure out (Straw is short for strawberry) but some on the other hand might night be as simple. (V.B.I.C. is commonly used to refer to Vanilla Bean Ice Cream) While you may never know all the shorthand for all the flavor concentrates out there, here are some of the common shorthands for major concentrate brands:\n\nThe Flavor Apprentice: TFA\nFlavor West: FW\nCapella: CAP\nFlavor Art: FA\nInawera: INW\nReal Flavors: RF\nFlavorah: FLV \n\nHopefullly, this helps you to find the right concentrates to buy if you decide to try out another DIYers Recipe and they use one of these shorthands</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">More Coming Soon!</string>
    <string name="understanding_ratios">A common difficulty that many people face when getting into the DIY scene, is understanding ratios and how they effect your measurements. Hopefully, we can shed some light on that for you. As you know, the end product is going to have a VG/PG ratio. (Usually 70/30, 80/20, or 50/50) This should be familiar. But dealing with ratios in mixing can be difficult. The things to remember are as follows: \n -Concentrates and Flavoring count as PG. 2% flavor in the mix takes up 2% of the total PG in the end ratio. \n -Your nicotine solution will have its own ratio. This is important. If you are working with 50/50 nicotine, and you put 6% of the bottle\'s volume in, that counts for 3% of both VG and PG for your end ratio. \n -What\'s known as \'flat\' PG and VG (No Nic 100%) should be added last, as they will take up the rest of the ratio that isn\'t handled by nicotine or flavoring. \n -Using 100mg nicotine will make all of your measurements easier, as 1% volume is equivilant to 1mg/mL and figuring out the impact on ratio will be easier.</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_app_title">How to: Use this App</string>
    <string name="flavor_mixing_tips_title">Flavor Mixing Tips</string>
    <string name="common_shorthands_title">Common Shorthands in the DIY Community</string>
    <string name="understanding_ratios_title">Understanding Ratios</string>
    <string name="thats_all_title">That\'s All for now!</string>
    <string name="example_recipes_disclaimer">*All Example Recipes are set to 120ml size, 3mg Nicotine, and 70/30 ratio by default using 100mg VG nicotine solution*</string>
    <string name="example_recipes_title">Example Recipes</string>
    <string name="_0_0ml">0.0mL</string>
    <string name="pg">PG:</string>
    <string name="vg">VG:</string>
    <string name="nicotine">Nicotine:</string>
    <string name="recipe_profile_hint">Recipe Profile</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_hint">Recipe Name</string>
    <string name="edit_recipe_button">Edit Recipe</string>
    <string name="results_title">Results</string>
    <string name="save_recipe_button">Save Recipe</string>
    <string name="saved_recipes_title">Saved Recipes</string>
    <string name="bottle_size">Bottle Size:</string>
    <string name="desired_strength">Desired Strength:</string>
    <string name="ml_hint">mL</string>
    <string name="mg_ml_hint">mg/mL</string>
    <string name="ratio_placeholder">50%</string>
    <string name="desired_ratio">Desired Ratio</string>
    <string name="nicotine_base_title">Nicotine Base</string>
    <string name="nicotine_base_strength">Nicotine Base Strength:</string>
    <string name="nicotine_base_ratio">Nicotine Base Ratio</string>
    <string name="next_page_flavors_button">Next Page: Flavors</string>
    <string name="step_2_flavors_title">Step 2 - Flavors</string>
    <string name="add_flavor_button">Add flavor</string>
    <string name="results_button">Results</string>
</resources>
